makingmoneywitharticles.blogspot.com 2009-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Making Money Online with Articles

##  [ Privacy Policy ](http://makingmoneywitharticles.blogspot.com/2008/02/privacy-policy.html)

Brought to you by: **EJ Cooksey** | 2/04/2008 10:23:00 PM 

Nothing is more important to EJ Cooksey than protecting the private information of visitors to our site. Below you'll find information about our commitment to ensuring the privacy of your and your children's personally identifiable information (such as your full name, address, email address, telephone number and/or other identifying information) and preserving the integrity of the medium.

Please read the following carefully. If you have any questions or concerns, please send us an email at [ejcooksey@ejcooksey.com](mailto:ejcooksey@ejcooksey.com).

### Gathering and Use of Information

EJ Cooksey will never willfully disclose any personally identifiable information about our online audience to any third party without first receiving the user's permission. We do not collect personally identifiable information from our visitors other than what is supplied to us on a voluntary basis.

Visitors to the EJ Cooksey Web Site may voluntarily supply certain personally identifiable information in connection with (i)contest or sweepstakes registration, (ii) subscription registration for sites or services which require subscription (such as email newsletters), (iii) requests for membership information and (iv) e-commerce transactions. In addition, personally identifiable information is voluntarily provided in connection with certain content submissions, community postings (i.e., forums or bulletin boards), comments and suggestions, or voting.

EJ Cooksey may use such information only for conducting the activities stated above, for internal marketing and promotional purposes.  

Interest based advertising  

The [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web.  
  
Google and the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx):

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

By using this site, you signify your agreement to the terms and conditions of this EJ Cooksey Web Site Privacy Policy. If you donot agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use the site. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the EJ Cooksey Web Site following the posting of any changes to these terms shall mean that you have accepted those changes. If you have any questions or concerns, please email us at [ejcooksey@ejcooksey.com](mailto:ejcooksey@ejcooksey.com).
